Yusheng
유성
if you can't eat
먹을 수 없다면
Or I'll make you sushi.
아니면 내가 초밥을 만들어줄게.
Can I use your arm?
팔을 사용해도 될까요?
piece of cake
케이크 조각
I'm going to the hospital today
나 오늘 병원에 갈 거야
see someone
누군가를 만나다
looks like you
너처럼 생겼어
I was originally today
나 원래 오늘이었어
I'm going to the hospital too.
나도 병원에 갈 거야.
is that so
그렇습니까?
go to see friends
친구를 만나러 가다
Why don't you go?
왜 가지 않니?
died
사망 한
Deep condolences to you
깊은 애도를 표합니다
It has passed
지나갔다
I won't say it anymore
더 이상 말하지 않겠습니다
Where is your brother?
네 형은 어디에?
Has the problem been solved.
문제가 해결되었습니까?
I tried my best
난 최선을 다 했어
Can it be solved?
해결될 수 있나요?
Just depends on luck
그냥 운에 달려있습니다
some things
몇 가지
we have no control
우리는 통제할 수 없어
a bit troublesome
조금 귀찮다
Like falling dominoes
떨어지는 도미노처럼
1 person fell
1명이 떨어졌다
a series of reactions occur
일련의 반응이 일어난다
It seems that this is the trouble you have encountered recently
최근에 발생한 문제인 것 같습니다.
so many
너무 많아
I agree
나는 동의한다
if i lose my job
내가 직장을 잃으면
How about working part-time here?
여기서 아르바이트를 하는 건 어때요?
Understood
이해했다
what can I do?
어떡해?
Lobby
로비
you really can't work
너 정말 일 못 해
follow me
나를 따라와
smile at each other
서로 미소 짓다
not suitable for you
당신에게는 적합하지 않습니다
What do you think I can do?
내가 뭘 할 수 있을 것 같아?
be you
당신이 되세요
this may be the best job
이게 최고의 직업일지도 몰라
Logically speaking
논리적으로 말하자면
I don't like the way it's done
나는 그 방식이 마음에 들지 않는다.
Change company
회사 변경
please continue my daily work
일상 업무를 계속해주세요
I've been doing this for years
나는 수년간 이 일을 해왔습니다.
There are also certain resources
특정 리소스도 있습니다.
Don't change jobs easily
쉽게 직업을 바꾸지 마세요
outside world
외부 세계
Maybe it's just superficial greatness
아마도 그것은 단지 피상적인 위대함일 뿐입니다.
But my current job is
하지만 현재 직업은
i don't deserve it
난 그럴 자격이 없어
Things that have lost their value to you
당신에게 가치를 잃은 것들
in the eyes of others
다른 사람들의 눈에는
it might be worth it
그만한 가치가 있을지도 몰라
is that so
그렇습니까?
certainly
틀림없이
it's in your eyes
그것은 당신의 눈 속에 있습니다
Am I worthy?
나는 합당합니까?
you are with me
너는 나와 같이있어
cannot be measured by value
가치로 측정할 수 없다
You are me in Jinhai
당신은 진하이에 있는 나입니다
Important person
중요한 사람
taste
맛
I suddenly lost my appetite
갑자기 식욕이 떨어졌어요
how
어떻게
Which word is mine?
어떤 단어가 내 것인가요?
inspired you
당신에게 영감을 주었어요
I'm not that weak
나 그렇게 약한 사람 아니야
Brother's troubles
형제의 고민
not yet resolved
아직 해결되지 않았습니다
I still need to deal with
아직 처리해야 할 일이 있어
Believe me
나를 믿어
his troubles will be solved
그의 문제는 해결될 것이다
This is also a woman’s intuition
이것도 여자의 직감이다
Sorry for your food
음식 미안해
Have the opportunity
기회를 가지세요
show me your true self
너의 진정한 모습을 보여줘
Tianyang Brothers
천양 형제
Why did you come back?
왜 돌아왔나요?
I'm so anxious
너무 불안해요
I'm having a little trouble
좀 곤란해요
that person
저 사람
Is it dead?
죽었나요?
died
사망 한
Do they doubt us?
그들이 우리를 의심하나요?
I can't pay that much attention
나는 그렇게 많은 관심을 기울일 수 없다
Let’s go rescue Huang Zichen first.
먼저 황지진을 구출하러 가자.
call
부르다
work has been done
작업이 완료되었습니다
I already know
나는 이미 알고 있다
I would like to thank Manager Taka for his sincerity.
진심을 담아주신 타카 감독님께 감사의 말씀을 전하고 싶습니다.
let me know
알려줘요
When can Zicheng come back?
Zicheng은 언제 돌아올 수 있습니까?
I think it will come soon
곧 올 것 같아요
Would you like something to drink?
마실 것좀 드실 래요?
Thanks.
감사해요.
when this work is completed
이 작업이 완료되면
I can't look back
뒤를 돌아볼 수 없어
Night fog persists
밤안개가 지속되다
Demand more from us
우리에게 더 많은 것을 요구하세요
I know
알아요
Next
다음
like we fall
우리가 넘어지듯이
falling dominoes
떨어지는 도미노
Go together
함께 가세요
No chance to hit the brakes
브레이크를 밟을 기회가 없습니다
Thanks.
감사해요.
no matter what comes next
다음에 무슨 일이 있어도
Things are unpredictable
상황은 예측할 수 없습니다
be prepared
준비하다
I know
알아요
Next step
다음 단계
what are you going to do
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까?
Let’s wait until Huang Zicheng is safe.
황쯔청이 무사할 때까지 기다리자.
if you listen to me
당신이 내 말을 듣는다면
I think of a way to protect you
널 보호할 방법을 생각해
if i'm okay
내가 괜찮다면
How are you
어떻게 지내세요
Thank you, Brother Tianyang
고마워요, 천양 형제님
I have one more condition
조건이 하나 더 있어요
you
너
Don't give up Huang Zichen
포기하지 마세요 황지진
continue to participate
계속 참여하다
I know
알아요
I want to sever ties with him
그 사람과 인연을 끊고 싶다
All contacts
모든 연락처
Do you think you can do it yourself?
스스로 할 수 있다고 생각하시나요?
must
~ 해야 하다
if it's not my fault
내 잘못이 아니라면
Neither can he
그도 마찬가지다
just like now
지금처럼
They have been in the past few days
그들은 지난 며칠 동안
Can let people go
사람들을 보내줄 수 있어요
Leave the next thing to me
다음 일은 나에게 맡겨라
as necessary
필요에 따라
We will contact you
연락드리겠습니다
OK
좋아요
pull him up
그를 끌어 올려
Inject him
그를 주사하다
don't let me die
내가 죽게 두지 마세요
OK
좋아요
you are a lucky boy
당신은 운이 좋은 소년이에요
can someone help
누군가 도와줄 수 있나요
woke up
일어났다
What have they done for me?
그들이 나에게 무슨 짓을 한 걸까요?
stabilizer
안정제
They are looking for you after all
그들은 결국 당신을 찾고 있습니다
You are in a good situation.
당신은 좋은 상황에 있습니다.
Yao Yao sent
야오야오가 보냈어요
elder brother
형
Welcome back
돌아온 것을 환영합니다
Have you eaten yet?
아직 식사하셨나요?
I haven't eaten it yet
아직 안 먹어봤어
I haven't eaten yet. I'll go make you some.
아직 밥도 안 먹었는데 가서 좀 만들어줄게.
you
너
Don't be too emotional
너무 감정적으로 굴지 마세요
It's Yaoyao
야오야오입니다
I think you're exposed
노출된 것 같아요
sooner or later
조만간
I just didn't expect it to be so early
이렇게 일찍 올 줄은 몰랐어
But why would she do this?
그런데 그녀는 왜 이런 짓을 했을까?
spies may become suspicious
스파이가 의심받을 수 있다
your identity
당신의 정체성
Exposure is not necessarily a bad thing
노출이 반드시 나쁜 것은 아닙니다
What does it mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
when they have questions
질문이 있을 때
You can cheat this time
이번엔 속일 수 있어
But next time I won't be able to hide it anymore
하지만 다음에는 더 이상 숨길 수 없을 거예요
Better yet, tell them
더 나은 방법은 그들에게 말하는 것입니다.
find your identity
당신의 정체성을 찾아보세요
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Give me
나에게주세요
send you away
너를 보내다
I'm not kidding
농담이 아냐
When did you do this?
언제 이런 일을 했나요?
I'm kidding
농담이야
You want them to come to you.
당신은 그들이 당신에게 오기를 원합니다.
if my identity is revealed
내 신원이 공개된다면
this is for them
이건 그들을 위한 거야
you have no value
넌 가치가 없어
you
너
Apart from
와는 별개로
They're using me to blackmail you.
그들은 당신을 협박하기 위해 나를 이용하고 있습니다.
Yes
예
How are you
어떻게 지내세요
Of course I have ways to deal with them.
물론 나에게는 그들을 다룰 방법이 있다.
listen to me
내 말 좀 들어봐
Don't be impulsive when in danger
위험할 때 충동적으로 행동하지 마세요
protect yourself
자신을 보호하다
don't do anything else
다른 일은 하지 마세요
Although I'm a little dissatisfied
조금 불만족스럽긴 하지만
but this time
하지만 이번에는
I made you do the right thing
나는 당신이 옳은 일을 하게 만들었어요
I told you
내가 말했잖아
Don’t be impulsive when encountering danger
위험에 직면했을 때 충동적으로 행동하지 마세요
why are you rebellious
왜 반항적이야?
This is my desire for life
이것이 내 삶의 소망이다
Tony is a suspicious person.
토니는 의심스러운 사람이에요.
if i'm quiet
내가 조용히 있으면
elusive
피하는
He must be doubting me
그 사람은 나를 의심하고 있는 게 틀림없어
It tastes like it's been submerged in sea water.
마치 바닷물에 잠긴 듯한 맛이 납니다.
it's painful
고통스럽다
I am very smart myself
나는 나 자신이 매우 똑똑하다
What is it used for?
그것은 무엇을 위해 사용됩니까?
let us do something for them
우리가 그들을 위해 뭔가를 해보자
What
무엇
Did not say
말하지 않았다
Confidentiality maintained
기밀 유지
I don't listen
나는 듣지 않는다
they promised me
그들은 나에게 약속했다
I won't bother you anymore
더 이상 귀찮게 하지 않을게
Where is Yaoyao?
야오야오는 어디에 있나요?
How did that happen?
어떻게 그런 일이 일어났나요?
I didn't see her
나는 그녀를 보지 못했다
she betrayed you
그녀는 당신을 배신했다
It's not worth worrying about her
그녀에 대해 걱정할 가치가 없어
She also has unavoidable difficulties.
그녀에게도 피할 수 없는 어려움이 있다.
The fog that night
그날 밤 안개
Threaten her family
그녀의 가족을 위협하다
when i soak in the sea
내가 바다에 몸을 담그면
i want to know everything
나는 모든 것을 알고 싶다
Night fog man
밤 안개 남자
You doubted me from the beginning
넌 처음부터 나를 의심했지
They asked me to steal data
그들은 나에게 데이터를 훔쳐달라고 요청했습니다
come try me
와서 날 시험해봐
They are already sunny
벌써 맑아졌네요
Still using me
아직도 나를 이용하고 있어
come try me
와서 날 시험해봐
I am not Yaoyao who was sold.
나는 팔린 야오야오가 아니다.
She bugged you.
그녀는 당신을 괴롭혔습니다.
I'll also take you to the fishing boat.
낚시배까지 데려다줄게요.
Yes
예
I think she threatened people.
내 생각엔 그녀가 사람들을 위협한 것 같아요.
That wasn't her intention
그건 그녀의 의도가 아니었어
There's no need to run away for her
그녀를 위해 도망칠 필요는 없어
whether forced or not
강제든 아니든
she is a spy
그녀는 스파이다
take a look
구경하다
She knows both of us
그 사람은 우리 둘 다 알아요
been touched
만져졌다
perhaps
아마도
but she didn't say
하지만 그녀는 말하지 않았어
Night fog man
밤 안개 남자
What does it mean
무슨 뜻이에요
She said she wanted to go ashore
그녀는 해변으로 가고 싶다고 말했어요
But no chance
하지만 기회는 없어
she is the last
그녀는 마지막이다
What did you say to me?
나한테 뭐라고 했어?
if i am early
내가 일찍 오면
i should tell her
내가 그녀에게 말해야겠어
Huang Zicheng
황쯔쳉
Ask me clearly
명확하게 물어보세요
this is not a game
이건 게임이 아니야
Not so much
별로
I know
알아요
I won't run away for her
나는 그녀를 위해 도망치지 않을 것이다
I just want to tell you
난 단지 당신에게 말하고 싶어
she's not completely corrupt
그녀는 완전히 부패하지 않았습니다
she still has hope
그녀에겐 아직 희망이 있어
if there is a chance
기회가 있다면
See if you can.
당신이 할 수 있는지 확인하십시오.
save her
그녀를 구해줘
This is a brutal killing
이건 잔혹한 살인이다
instead of saving fallen souls
타락한 영혼을 구하는 대신
do you understand
이해했나요
knew
알고 있었다
If she still has hope in her heart
그녀의 마음속에 아직 희망이 있다면
She will teach with her actions
그녀는 행동으로 가르칠 것이다
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
you can exit
나가면 돼
end
끝
When you are done with me I will throw me away
네가 나랑 끝나면 난 날 버릴 거야
I won't abandon you
나는 당신을 버리지 않을 것입니다
The spy abandoned you
스파이가 당신을 버렸어요
you have landed
당신은 착륙했습니다
later action
이후 조치
you don't need to join
넌 가입할 필요 없어
But before the event is over
하지만 행사가 끝나기도 전에
Be careful
조심하세요
if they contact you
그 사람이 너한테 연락하면
contact me anytime
언제든지 연락주세요
The game is?
게임은?
Should I continue?
계속해야 하나요?
let go
놓아줘
If I need you I will go to you
당신이 필요하면 당신에게 갈게요
It doesn't matter
그것은 중요하지 않습니다
For you
당신을 위한
Just go back to the beginning
그냥 처음으로 돌아가세요
Now
지금
I'm not the same anymore
나는 더 이상 예전과 같지 않아요
I'll send you the address
주소 보내드릴게요
see you later.
나중에 봐요.
OK
좋아요
This is a secret base
이곳은 비밀기지입니다
Qin area
진 지역
Sorry Wu Xi
미안 우시
we give you
우리는 당신에게
I hid this
나는 이것을 숨겼다
It seemed like I was the only one surrounded by the sound of drums
북소리에 둘러싸인 건 나뿐인 것 같았어
sit down
앉아
you are part of the plan
당신은 계획의 일부입니다
your plan is
당신의 계획은
since when
언제부터
I discovered Yaoyao
야오야오를 발견했어요
I began to doubt Huang Zichen's identity.
나는 황지진의 정체가 의심되기 시작했다.
Do you remember Yaoyao?
야오야오를 기억하시나요?
Can you treat me to dinner?
저한테 저녁 대접해주실 수 있나요?
when she just came back from thailand
그녀가 방금 태국에서 돌아왔을 때
meal time
식사 시간
I found the details
자세한 내용을 찾았습니다
Your phone case is nice.
휴대폰 케이스가 예쁘네요.
Yao Yao sent
야오야오가 보냈어요
She suddenly gave Huang Zichen a gift.
그녀는 갑자기 황지진에게 선물을 주었다.
1 mobile phone case
휴대폰 케이스 1개
I have a little doubt
나는 조금 의심한다
I'll check it out
제가 그것을 확인해 보겠습니다
There's a bug inside
안에 벌레가 있어요
At that moment I was convinced
그 순간 나는 확신했다.
Huang Zichen’s identity
황지진의 아이덴티티
has been exposed
노출되었습니다
Sooner or later he will take action against Huang Zichen.
조만간 그는 Huang Zichen에 대해 조치를 취할 것입니다.
so do something
그러니 뭐 좀 해봐
give them a goal
그들에게 목표를 줘
forwarded to you
당신에게 전달
Yes
예
I did it on purpose
일부러 그랬지
Secrets from the National Security Agency
국가안전보위부의 비밀
secretly
남몰래
Help Huang Zicheng's virtual image
Huang Zicheng의 가상 이미지를 도와주세요
Just at this time
바로 이 시간에
Shoichi caused the accident.
쇼이치가 사고를 일으켰습니다.
Then Yogiri started trying.
그런 다음 요기리는 노력하기 시작했습니다.
He has
그는 가지고있다
Huang Zicheng came to threaten me.
황자성이 나를 위협하러 왔다.
Let's kill Shoichi.
쇼이치를 죽여보자.
Was it your hand?
당신 손이었나요?
No
아니요
I propose to Yogiri
요기리에게 프로포즈해요
I need help
도움이 필요해요
on this occasion
이번 기회에
You can pull this boss out
이 상사를 끌어낼 수 있어요
but i never thought
하지만 난 생각해본 적 없어
He asked Yaoyao to act.
그는 Yaoyao에게 행동을 요청했습니다.
So you took advantage of Yaoyao
그래서 당신은 Yaoyao를 이용했습니다
Yes
예
people in morgue
영안실에 있는 사람들
Probably not Soo Yi
아마 수이는 아닐 거야
certainly
틀림없이
body bag zipper
바디백 지퍼
Did you do any tricks?
무슨 속임수라도 썼나요?
they are difficult to open
그것들은 열기가 어렵다
Don't let people find out
사람들이 알아차리지 못하게 하세요
Do you think Mr. Zhang will go?
장 씨가 갈 것 같아요?
she doesn't believe me
그 사람은 나를 믿지 않아
She will definitely go
그녀는 확실히 갈 것이다
The show is for them
쇼는 그들을 위한 것이다
Very important
매우 중요
Your plan is so detailed
계획이 너무 구체적이군요
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
왜 더 일찍 말하지 않았나요?
because you are right
당신 말이 맞으니까
Suspects about Sauer's death
사우어의 죽음에 대한 용의자
It's also part of our plan
그것도 우리 계획의 일부야
everything went smoothly
모든 일이 순조롭게 진행됐다
Even people who look at me are suspicious.
나를 보는 사람들조차 의심을 품는다.
your concerns
당신의 우려
Just hiding my danger
내 위험을 숨기고 있을 뿐이야
even if you tell me
네가 나한테 말해도
I will also cooperate
나도 협력할게
The fog from the previous night shrouded Yaoyao.
전날 밤의 안개가 야오야오를 가렸다.
A listening device was installed
청취 장치가 설치되었습니다
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
Is there eyeliner around me?
내 주변에 아이라이너가 있나요?
I did not notice
나는 통보하지 않았다
that's why i decided
그게 내가 결정한 이유야
this drama
이 드라마
the truth
진실
I agree
나는 동의한다
Your stations are connected to each other
스테이션이 서로 연결되어 있습니다
If there is even the slightest omission
조금이라도 누락된 부분이 있다면
i will lose everything
나는 모든 것을 잃을 것이다
that's why
그렇기 때문에
Must be careful
조심해야 해
Wuxi
우시
You are now officially joining
이제 공식적으로 합류하게 되었습니다.
Become a Fisherman Project Member
어부 프로젝트 회원이 되세요
forest plan
산림 계획
here we go
여기 간다
Current Director of the Fisherman Project
현재 어부 프로젝트 이사
We are not in the Tianjin Hai Bureau.
우리는 천진하이국에 속하지 않습니다.
in the security department
보안 부서에서
You look like Director Zhao.
자오 감독님 닮았네요.
and other engineers
그리고 다른 엔지니어들
Everything is borrowed from the ministries.
모든 것은 부처에서 빌린 것입니다.
with the two people in front of you
네 앞에 있는 두 사람과 함께
all ministries
모든 사역
The detective who was transferred
전근된 형사
This special operations group
이 특수 작전 그룹
behind the scenes
무대 뒤에서
support this action
이 행동을 지지하다
Fisherman's plan goals
어부의 계획 목표
What
무엇
Xinglin behavior
Xinglin의 행동
this is a huge plan
이건 엄청난 계획이야
The first step is to look up at the sun
첫 번째 단계는 태양을 바라보는 것이다.
Win Mr. Zhang’s trust
장 씨의 신뢰를 얻으세요
through her
그녀를 통해
Tsui's spy network
Tsui의 스파이 네트워크
eradicate
근절하다
since it was discovered
그것이 발견된 이후로
Mr. Zhang
장 씨
Why can't we catch it directly?
왜 직접 잡을 수 없나요?
because
왜냐하면
This Mr. Zhang is playing a game.
이 장씨는 게임을 하고 있습니다.
There is another one online
온라인에 또 하나 있어요
in spy games
스파이 게임에서
Yes
예
She and this person
그 사람과 이 사람
Please contact me only during games
경기중에만 연락주세요
This person's name is Z
이 사람 이름은 Z예요
He is in control
그는 통제하고 있다
of all industries
모든 산업의
User repository
사용자 저장소
As long as Mr. Zhang is here
장 씨가 여기 있는 한
what kind of person do you need
어떤 사람이 필요해요?
tell him
그에게 말해
He can give you some goals
그는 당신에게 몇 가지 목표를 줄 수 있습니다
and their materials
그리고 그들의 재료
Who is Z?
Z는 누구인가?
we don't even know
우리는 심지어 모른다
Maybe Mr. Zhang
아마도 장 씨
I don't know who it is
누군지 모르겠어요
and
그리고
Mr. Zhang holds it in his hand.
장 씨가 그것을 손에 쥐고 있습니다.
Another trump card
또 다른 트럼프 카드
Hidden within biota
생물군 내에 숨겨져 있음
before us
우리 앞에
I always thought it was Huang Zichen
난 항상 황지첸이라고 생각했는데
This is their trump card
이것이 그들의 비장의 카드다
at this point
이 지점에서
He is just a tool
그 사람은 도구일 뿐이야
Is the news reliable?
그 소식은 믿을 만한가?
Sauce
소스
A man was abandoned in the night fog
한 남자가 밤안개 속에 버려졌다
Shore wakes up
쇼어가 깨어났다
Wuxi
우시
You were involved in this operation
당신은 이 작전에 참여했습니다
The goal is to find it
그것을 찾는 것이 목표이다
in game
게임 중
I can understand one thing
한 가지는 이해할 수 있어요
User materials for various industries
다양한 산업 분야의 사용자 자료
database user
데이터베이스 사용자
Z
지
give it to me
그걸 나에게주세요
Tianyang
텐양
You continue to contact Mr. Zhang.
당신은 계속해서 장 씨에게 연락하고 있습니다.
Find all her offline status
그녀의 오프라인 상태를 모두 찾아보세요
Especially hidden things
특히 숨겨진 것들
within biological group
생물학적 그룹 내에서
That trump card
그 트럼프 카드
make out
알아내다
feels good
좋은 느낌
This answered my heart
이것이 내 마음에 응답했다
big problem
큰 문제
Yogiri is on a secret service mission.
요기리는 비밀 임무를 수행하고 있습니다.
what is developing
무엇이 발전하고 있나요?
The origins of gamers
게이머의 기원
High probability
높은 확률
This is Mr. Z
미스터 Z입니다
You can provide a repository like this
다음과 같은 저장소를 제공할 수 있습니다.
Most likely a major site
메이저 사이트일 가능성이 높음
of these users
이 사용자 중
Work and life information
일과 생활 정보
Yes
예
But there are many such websites
그런데 그런 사이트가 너무 많아요
Find players we know
우리가 아는 선수 찾기
Find out what they signed up for
그들이 무엇에 가입했는지 알아보세요
Applicable websites
적용 가능한 웹사이트
I think you'll find it soon
금방 찾으실 것 같아요
able
할 수 있는
I have a hunch
예감이 들어요
this clue
이 단서
may help us
우리에게 도움이 될 수 있습니다
Basically
원래
Eliminate spy games in one go
스파이 게임을 한 번에 제거하세요
that's optimistic
그거 낙관적이야
Of course that is
물론 그렇죠
I'm not you
나는 당신이 아니다
everything
모든 것
I only want bad things
난 나쁜 것만 원해
I was doing this so deeply by myself all day long.
나는 하루 종일 혼자서 이 짓을 하고 있었습니다.
but you know
하지만 너도 알지
I still praise you
나는 아직도 당신을 칭찬합니다
Planning is tightly cyclical.
계획은 주기적으로 진행됩니다.
Protect Huang Zicheng
황자성을 보호하라
I brought Principal Zhang out.
나는 장 교장을 데리고 나왔다.
I also earned her trust in you.
나는 또한 당신에 대한 그녀의 신뢰를 얻었습니다.
Even if you say so, I'm amazing.
그렇게 말해도 나는 참 대단하다.
this is a bit disappointing
이건 좀 실망스럽다
if she wasn't alone
그녀가 혼자가 아니었다면
spy story
스파이 이야기
you two are
너희 둘은
this is perfect for you
이것은 당신에게 완벽합니다
I approached her
나는 그녀에게 다가갔다
Because I think she's suspicious.
내 생각엔 그녀가 의심스럽다고 생각하기 때문이다.
hope so
그러길 바라
this is not the end
이게 끝이 아니야
What are you going to do now?
지금 무엇을 할 예정 이니?
You're not done yet.
아직 끝나지 않았습니다.
The ones I mentioned are Huang Zicheng and Yao Yao.
제가 언급한 분들은 황쯔청(Huang Zicheng)과 야오야오(Yao Yao)입니다.
Yaoyao didn't touch her first.
Yaoyao는 그녀를 먼저 만지지 않았습니다.
She is my best support
그녀는 나의 최고의 지원입니다
Huang Zicheng
황쯔쳉
I've sent him out
내가 그를 보냈어요
you replaced
당신이 교체했습니다
Huang Zicheng’s location
황쯔청(Huang Zicheng)의 위치
He and Yaoyao
그와 야오야오
divided into
로 나누어
Can it be divided?
나누어질 수 있나요?
Even if you can't split it, you still get points.
분할하지 못하더라도 포인트를 얻을 수 있습니다.
now in his mind
지금 그의 마음 속에
That must be sad
그건 슬픈 일이겠죠
You said this person really doesn't talk.
이 사람 정말 말을 안 한다고 하더군요.
I'm driving.
난 운전 중이 야.
what are you saying
당신이 무슨 말을하는거야
Just believe me
그냥 나를 믿으세요
feeling abandoned
버림받은 느낌
don't comfort him
그 사람을 위로하지 마세요
no need
필요 없음
bad
나쁜
The mission went smoothly
임무는 순조롭게 진행됐다
I didn't misunderstand you
나는 당신을 오해하지 않았습니다
That promise is
그 약속은
Turn it into cash quickly
빨리 현금으로 바꾸세요
certainly
틀림없이
Your sister can leave at any time
네 여동생은 언제든지 떠날 수 있어
promise
약속하다
OK
좋아요
I?
나?
is that so
그렇습니까?
I can leave Jinhai.
진하이를 떠날 수 있어요.
You are in Jinhai
당신은 진하이에 있습니다
I have other responsibilities
나에게는 다른 책임이 있다
The purpose of dragging Huang Zichen into the water
황자진을 물속으로 끌고 간 목적
Just to control Huang Jiaming.
Huang Jiaming을 통제하기 위해서입니다.
Now Huang Zicheng
이제 황쯔쳉(Huang Zicheng)
It’s no longer valuable
더 이상 가치가 없어
The scorching sun is also coming for you
뜨거운 태양도 당신을 위해 온다
draw water
물을 길어오다
Leave me in Jinhai
나를 진하이에 남겨두세요
Useless
쓸모 없는
How could you leave in such a hurry?
어떻게 그렇게 서둘러 떠날 수 있었나요?
i killed someone
내가 누군가를 죽였어
It's too dangerous to stay here
여기에 머무르는 것은 너무 위험해요
It's safe to return to headquarters.
본부로 돌아가도 안전합니다.
you do not need to worry
걱정할 필요 없어
Jinjing now
지금 진징
your best place
당신의 가장 좋은 장소
Why
왜
Gao Tianyang has arrived at Jinhai.
Gao Tianyang이 Jinhai에 도착했습니다.
mobile umbrella
모바일 우산
as long as you need
당신이 필요로하는 한
he will help you work
그 사람이 당신이 일하는 것을 도와줄 거예요
come back now
지금 돌아와
Such a relationship is a waste
그런 관계는 낭비야
but i still
하지만 난 아직도
What tasks will you perform?
어떤 작업을 수행할 예정인가요?
The organization has plans
조직에는 계획이 있다
when i
내가 언제
to complete the task
작업을 완료하기 위해
hope
희망
I can do it forever
영원히 할 수 있어
You still here
당신 아직 여기 있군요
I want to be with Huang Zichen
황지진과 함께하고 싶다
You are me and him
당신은 나와 그 사람입니다
Is it okay?
괜찮나요?
if he knows you
그 사람이 당신을 안다면
Kill for him
그를 위해 죽여라
terribly sorry
정말 죄송 해요
but you already are
하지만 당신은 이미
I promise to heaven
천국에 약속해요
you promised heaven
당신은 천국을 약속했어요
I won't use yellow anymore.
이제 노란색은 사용하지 않겠습니다.
I don't use him
나는 그를 사용하지 않습니다
You still here
당신 아직 여기 있군요
Face things you can't control
통제할 수 없는 일에 맞서세요
You must learn to accept
받아들이는 법을 배워야 한다
enjoy
즐기다
OK
좋아요
But I have one more thing to do.
그런데 한 가지 더 할 일이 있어요.
I don't want any more interceptions
더 이상 차단을 원하지 않습니다.
continue
계속하다
no problem
괜찮아요
I believe you now.
나는 이제 당신을 믿습니다.
You sent me home suddenly
갑자기 날 집에 보냈잖아
what happened
무슨 일이에요
elder sister
언니
I've been doing this for a while
나는 한동안 이 일을 해왔다.
I can't explain it to you either.
나도 당신에게 설명할 수 없어요.
I can only tell you
난 너에게만 말할 수 있어
being threatened
위협을 받고 있다
They threaten me with your safety
그들은 당신의 안전을 위협합니다
threaten
위협하다
Who are you?
누구세요?
Did you report the crime to the police?
범죄를 경찰에 신고하셨나요?
I have no choice
어쩔수없이
i will tell you everything
내가 너에게 모든 걸 말해줄게
The police can't control this
경찰은 이를 통제할 수 없다
just if
만약에
You have been in the United States.
당신은 미국에 있었습니다.
they will continue to threaten me
그들은 계속해서 나를 위협할 것이다
Trying to blackmail me into doing something
나한테 뭔가를 하라고 협박하려고 해
what i don't want to do
내가 하고 싶지 않은 것
But my current job is
하지만 현재 직업은
Will you listen to me this time?
이번엔 내 말 좀 들어줄래?
You can look for it again after you get back from get off work.
퇴근 후 다시 찾아보시면 됩니다.
I just want to
나는 그저 원할 뿐이야
Both of us
우리 둘 다
peace, security
평화, 안보
living together
동거하다
I can
저 할 수 있어요
OK
좋아요
i listen to you
너 한테 귀 기울이고있어
We look forward to your return.
우리는 귀하의 복귀를 기대하고 있습니다.
What we know so far
우리가 지금까지 알고 있는 것
game player
게임 플레이어
All users browsing the site
사이트를 탐색하는 모든 사용자
of which pure
그 중 순수한
Shi Lei
시 레이
Zhu Yan
주얀
sunny
화창한
All from the Tetsuzo website
모두 Tetsuzo 웹사이트에서
Deep users
심층 사용자
Read aloud
소리내어 읽기
Yes
예
I'm currently learning about
나는 현재 다음과 같은 내용을 배우고 있습니다.
Client work information
클라이언트 업무정보
Hobby website
취미 웹사이트
Not so much
별로
But Tetsuya is one of them.
하지만 테츠야도 그중 하나다.
So far we have not disclosed
지금까지 우리는 공개하지 않았습니다
one question
하나의 질문
Agent task selection mechanism
에이전트 작업 선택 메커니즘
What should I do if it’s foggy at night?
밤에 안개가 끼면 어떻게 해야 하나요?
among a huge user base
거대한 사용자 기반 중
Choose the one that is most useful to them
그들에게 가장 유용한 것을 선택하십시오
excellent player
우수한 선수
and pull them into the water
그리고 물속으로 끌어당겨
Read aloud
소리내어 읽기
Currently domestic
현재 국내
The most professional influence
가장 전문적인 영향
Q&A session
Q&A 세션
it contains many things
그것은 많은 것을 담고 있다
Professional positions
전문직
People who like to visit this site
이 사이트를 방문하고 싶은 사람들
academically
학문적으로
There is a certain threshold
일정한 기준점이 있어요
some of them
그들 중 일부
contains a lot
많이 들어있다
people who work confidentially
비밀리에 일하는 사람들
Like Shi Lei
시 레이처럼
Zhu Yan
주얀
sunny
화창한
or participate in
또는 참여하다
Major-related students
전공관련학생
just like dad
아빠처럼
Yes
예
target audience
타겟 고객
Covered up spies
은폐된 스파이
a group of people you want to attract
당신이 끌어들이고 싶은 사람들의 그룹
If the night fog comes
밤안개가 오면
User information by industry
업종별 사용자 정보
can be easily pulled
쉽게 당길 수 있다
desired goal
원하는 목표
later
나중에
make believe
믿게 하다
Philosophical reading and spy games
철학적 독서와 스파이 게임
I'm sure there's a connection
확실히 연관이 있는 것 같아
Yao Yao
야오야오
Yes
예
Yaoyao is a philosopher.
야오야오는 철학자이다.
This may not be a coincidence
이건 우연이 아닐지도 몰라
Your guess is
당신의 추측은
convincing
설득력 있는
but
하지만
Again, there is not enough evidence to support this
다시 말하지만, 이를 뒷받침할 증거가 충분하지 않습니다.
right now we
지금 우리는
We still need to break through
아직은 돌파해야 해
I think Yaoyao knows.
내 생각에는 야오야오가 알고 있는 것 같다.
Is there a relationship between reading philosophy and games?
철학 읽기와 게임 사이에 관계가 있나요?
she shouldn't know
그 사람은 몰라야 해
I think
제 생각에는
Mr. Z in the game
게임 속 미스터 Z
hidden in philosophy
철학 속에 숨겨진
if we can find him
우리가 그를 찾을 수 있다면
this is the best
이게 최선이다
Thanks.
감사해요.
Please give me a glass of the same thing.
같은 것 한 잔 주세요.
OK
좋아요
How long have we not seen each other?
우리가 서로 보지 못한 지 얼마나 됐나요?
1 week
일주
haven't seen you for a long time
오랫동안 당신을 보지 못했어요
After disembarking
하선 후
what have you done
당신은 무엇을 했나요?
i know everything
나는 모든 것을 알고 있다
Little Tianyou taught me
Little Tianyou가 나에게 가르쳐주었습니다.
Pull the Kokuan people into the water
코쿠안 사람들을 물속으로 끌어들이세요
You know
알잖아
Is this serious?
심각한가요?
I know
알아요
but i have to do it
하지만 난 해야 해
you really don't need
넌 정말 필요 없어
come and save me
와서 나를 구해주세요
so
그래서
yourself
당신 자신
looks important
중요해 보인다
The person who wants to save you is Gao Tianyang.
당신을 구하고 싶은 사람은 Gao Tianyang입니다.
Yogiri takes advantage of this.
요기리는 이를 이용합니다.
I am originally a night fog person.
저는 원래 밤안개를 좋아하는 사람이에요.
This is the mission they gave me.
이것이 그들이 나에게 준 사명이다.
Task# Task#
작업# 작업#
I can't even say
말할 수도 없어
this is not your fault
이건 네 잘못이 아니야
In the end we both
결국 우리 둘 다
get acquainted
익숙해
but
하지만
we all cheated on each other
우리는 모두 서로를 속였어
but i can't
하지만 난 못해
I will leave you to die alone.
나는 당신을 혼자 죽게 내버려 둘 것입니다.
so save you
그러니 당신을 구해주세요
in order to complete the mission
임무를 완수하기 위해
Are you still helping Yogiri do his job?
아직도 요기리의 일을 돕고 있나요?
Are there any other options?
다른 옵션이 있나요?
practical things
실용적인 것들
Things are not as bad as you think
생각보다 상황이 나쁘지는 않습니다
I know you are threatened
나는 당신이 위협을 받고 있다는 것을 알고 있습니다
you still have a chance
너에겐 아직 기회가 있어
be a hero
영웅이 되라
you can't save anything
당신은 아무것도 저장할 수 없습니다
you forget
당신은 잊었다
avoid these things
이런 것들을 피하세요
Finally landed
드디어 착륙했다
Stop participating
참여 중지
I can
저 할 수 있어요
It's over between us
우리 사이는 끝났어
From the moment you step on the plane
비행기에 탑승하는 순간부터
It's over now
끝이야
That's why I'm leaving no stone unturned today
그래서 오늘은 아무 것도 남기지 않을 거야
chose this place
이곳을 선택했어요
I was just thinking
난 그냥 생각하고 있었어요
where does it start
어디서 시작돼?
end somewhere
어딘가에서 끝나다
sounds good
좋은 것 같아요
I like this sense of ceremony
이런 세레모니한 느낌이 좋아
this looks slick
이거 매끈해 보여
Do you regret it?
후회하시나요?
what do you regret
뭘 후회해?
I regret knowing you
당신을 알고 후회해요
return
반품
sorry for what we went through
우리가 겪은 일에 대해 미안해
Nothing to regret
후회할 건 없어
It's impossible anyway
어차피 불가능해
let's try again
다시 해보자
rather than clinging to it
거기에 매달리기보다는
It would be better if you open your eyes a little wider
눈을 좀 더 크게 뜨면 좋을 것 같아요
go ahead
어서
we are in this world
우리는 이 세상에 있어요
everything is just one
모든 것은 하나뿐이야
small dust
작은 먼지
Not everyone is that important
모든 사람이 그렇게 중요한 것은 아니다
goodbye.
안녕히 가세요.